Heaven help us.
Religulous is a documentary, comedy film directed by Larry Charles.
Commentator-comic Bill Maher plays devil's advocate with
religion as he talks to believers about their faith.
Traveling around the world, Maher examines the tenets of Christianity, Judaism and Islam and raises questions
about homosexuality, proof of Christ's existence, Jewish Sabbath laws, violent Muslim extremists.
Self - Host/Narrator, played by Bill Maher.
Self, played by Jose Luis De Jesus Miranda.
Self, played by Andrew Newberg.
Self, played by Steve Burg.
Self, played by Tal Bachman.
Self, played by Jonathan Boulden.
Religulous () is a 2008 American documentary film written by and
starring comedian Bill Maher and directed by Larry Charles.
The title of the film is a portmanteau derived from
the words religious and ridiculous.
The documentary
examines and challenges religion and religious belief.
The film explores themes of muslim, faith, museum, rabbi, interview.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.